hhgregg.com 2017-05-08

# Privacy Policy

#### Information Practices

hhgregg understands that security and privacy are important to visitors to our hhgregg.com website, our mobile app (the "Sites") and to customers shopping at our stores or otherwise interacting with hhgregg (the “Services”) and we aim to keep your information secure and confidential. That is why we maintain the following standards to help protect information that personally identifies you and have described them in this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”).

**By using the Sites or Services you consent to our collection and use of your information as described in this Policy.**

#### Collection of Personal Information

You may be asked to voluntarily provide your name, billing address, shipping address, phone number, credit card number, email address or other personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") to make purchases online or in-store, to speak with our customer services representatives, or to otherwise access and enjoy the Sites or Services.

We or our business partners may also collect information automatically, such as your IP or MAC address (a number used to identify your computer or mobile device on the Internet), information about your location, or the type of browser you are using through the use of cookies or by other means. We hope that, by using this information, we can update the Sites to be more useful to you and other users.

#### Use of Information

hhgregg uses your Personal Information for the following purposes: to process your orders and administer your account; to administer and improve the Sites and related services; to notify you of our products, services, promotional events or special offers that may be of interest to you; to notify you of product recalls or other product safety communications; to provide Internet security; and to meet legal requirements such as responding to a subpoena. hhgregg may work with our business partners who may perform certain functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, sending email messages, managing data, processing credit card payments or providing customer service. These business partners have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these specific functions and may not use it for any other purpose. hhgregg also may share your Personal Information with our manufacturers, vendors or others in connection with product recalls or other product safety undertakings.  Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally required to do so.

We may use third-party advertising companies to place ads on the Sites and to place our ads on other websites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements on the Sites and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. For more information on interest-based advertising, including how you may be able to opt-out, please visit: [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

In addition, hhgregg may participate in the Adobe Marketing Cloud Device Co-op to better understand how you use our Sites across the various devices you use and to deliver tailored promotions to you.  To learn more and manage your privacy please visit: [www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html)

If hhgregg is involved in the sale of a substantial portion of its business assets, Personal Information may be among the transferred assets.

#### Privacy of Children

hhgregg encourages parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their children's online activities. Our Sites are not directed at or intended for children. We strictly adhere to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not solicit or knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Information from any child under the age of 13 in any manner that violates this law.

#### Your Opportunity to Opt-out of Email Advertising

In the event you do not wish to receive promotional email from hhgregg, follow the opt-out instructions contained within the body of any email message you receive or contact us as provided below.

#### Cookies

When you visit the Sites, hhgregg or a third-party partner may store or recognize some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file that can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the Sites to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Sites may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Sites' features. Please recognize that hhgregg does not control third-party browser tools and cannot guarantee their effectiveness. 

#### Do Not Track

Some web browsers incorporate a Do Not Track (“DNT”) feature that signals to websites that you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. At the present time, there are not yet established and universal standards for recognizable DNT signals and therefore, the Sites do not recognize DNT.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

This Policy describes how we may share your Personal Information for marketing purposes. You may contact us with any questions and, to the extent applicable, to request once a calendar year a list of third parties to whom we may disclose information for their own marketing purposes and the categories of information we may disclose.

#### Links

The Sites may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. hhgregg is not responsible for the collection or use of your Personal Information at any third party sites.

#### Security

We use industry-standard policies and procedures to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information that we collect and maintain. All Personal Information is stored on our secured servers, behind a firewall at a data center with access to data strictly controlled. Any unauthorized use of the Sites may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution. hhgregg uses current industry-standard techniques to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it transmits over the Internet.

#### Updates to this Policy

We may modify this Policy at any time, and, accordingly, we urge you to frequently review the Policy. The Personal Information we gather now will be subject to the Policy in effect at the time of use.  We may contact you with notices regarding this Policy, but you can find the current version of this Policy posted on our Sites.

#### Contacting hhgregg or Modifying Your Personal Information

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy and would like to modify or request that we make changes to or delete your Personal Information, please [contact us](https://www.hhgregg.com/service/CustomerService). Please provide a concise communication with complete information, including your contact information.

This Privacy Policy was last updated:  October 2016
